[Music]
game.
All right, game face on. Are you even
trying? Attack the objective. Uh, yeah.
Bailing out. Blizzard games. That's so
old school. Oh, boo. They're moving the
payload. Boosters engaged. Clear the
area. Come on, you can do it. Defend the
objective. Don't give up. Don't mess
with me. Don't worry, I've got this.
Diva one, bad guy zero. Diva online.
Lol.
Enemy teleporter located. Enemy turret.
Epic. Fall back. Game on. Get owned. Get
owned.
[Laughter]
GHF.
Great team play.
Enemies on the point. Let's clear them
out.
Hats.
GG.
Hey, they have a teleporter. Hey, try
and keep up. Okay. High score for sure.
HP max. I can't wait to get into the
fight. I need shields. I thought you
were going to be a challenge now. Show
them.
I'll take more of that. I'm going in.
I'm going to have to shoot you down. I'm
just getting warmed up. I'm not a good
loser. I'm on a roll. I'm on defense.
I'm too young to die. I'm with you. I've
got your back. In five, four, 3, two,
one. Is this easy mode?
Last round. This is where it counts.
Let's finish this right now. Let's shoot
for a new high score. Level up.
Of course. Here you go. Love, diva.
Minor setback, but we can still win
this. Move the payload. Moving the
payload. Let's party up. MVP diva. Nerf
this. New objective. Get the payload
moving. Nice shot. No one's beating my
high scores. No. Now that's teamwork.
NS.
Nuh-uh.
Oh, that'll be play of the game.
Oh, you must like me.
Payload moving. Let's all work together.
Payload's moving. Get on it. Payload's
moving. Let's knock them back. Payload
stopped. Let's get it moving. Play of
the game. Press start to continue.
Ready, player one.
Save that for the Hall of Fame. Score
multiplier.
Sniper, don't get caught. Suiting up.
Take out the target. Taking off. Thanks
for your support.
Thanks. That one's for my fans. There's
no way I'm losing. Attack. They're
taking the point. Time to get some
kills. Think you can keep up with me?
This is it. Come on, team. This point
has my name written all over it. Time's
running out. Everyone attack. Ultimate
ready. Up, up, down, down, left, right,
left, right. Ba. Start. We've got this.
Don't let up now.
What did I get? Winky face.
You can't be serious.
[Music]